export const submissions = [
    {
        id: 1, 
        userId: 2, 
        candidateName: 'John Smith', 
        company: 'Amazon', 
        role: 'React Developer', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 8, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 4, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Create a bathtub using JavaScript (preferably React). There should be a button that adds water to the tub, and a button that removes water. Bonus points if you can create this using React hooks.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Paste your GitHub repository here', 
        challengeAnswer: 'www.github.com', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional HTML experience do you have?", 
                answer: 5
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional CSS experience do you have?", 
                answer: 5
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional JavaScript experience do you have?", 
                answer: 5
            },  
            {
                question: "How many years of professional React experience do you have?", 
                answer: 5
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence:", 
                answer: "Full stack software engineer with 5 years of professional experience."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is the greatest invention?", 
                answer: "Wireless headphones."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite novel?", 
                answer: "Moby Dick"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 1, 
        userId: 3, 
        candidateName: 'Lisa Turner', 
        company: 'Amazon', 
        role: 'React Developer', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 6, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 4, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Create a bathtub using JavaScript (preferably React). There should be a button that adds water to the tub, and a button that removes water. Bonus points if you can create this using React hooks.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Paste your GitHub repository here', 
        challengeAnswer: 'www.github.com', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional HTML experience do you have?", 
                answer: 4
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional CSS experience do you have?", 
                answer: 4
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional JavaScript experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            },  
            {
                question: "How many years of professional React experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence:", 
                answer: "CSS Wizard."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is the greatest invention?", 
                answer: "Radar."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite novel?", 
                answer: "Crime and Punishment"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 1, 
        userId: 4, 
        candidateName: 'Jeffrey Davis',
        company: 'Amazon', 
        role: 'React Developer', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 7, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 4, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Create a bathtub using JavaScript (preferably React). There should be a button that adds water to the tub, and a button that removes water. Bonus points if you can create this using React hooks.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Paste your GitHub repository here', 
        challengeAnswer: 'www.github.com', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional HTML experience do you have?", 
                answer: 5
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional CSS experience do you have?", 
                answer: 5
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional JavaScript experience do you have?", 
                answer: 3
            },  
            {
                question: "How many years of professional React experience do you have?", 
                answer: 3
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence:", 
                answer: "Love the outdoors and writing code."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is the greatest invention?", 
                answer: "The telephone"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite novel?", 
                answer: "Life of Pi"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 1, 
        userId: 5, 
        candidateName: 'Marilyn Ross', 
        company: 'Amazon', 
        role: 'React Developer', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 5, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 4, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Create a bathtub using JavaScript (preferably React). There should be a button that adds water to the tub, and a button that removes water. Bonus points if you can create this using React hooks.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Paste your GitHub repository here', 
        challengeAnswer: 'www.github.com', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional HTML experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional CSS experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional JavaScript experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            },  
            {
                question: "How many years of professional React experience do you have?", 
                answer: 1
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence:", 
                answer: "Front end developer and copywriter."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is the greatest invention?", 
                answer: "35mm film camera"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite novel?", 
                answer: "Wuthering Heights"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 1, 
        userId: 6, 
        candidateName: 'Walter Jackson', 
        company: 'Amazon', 
        role: 'React Developer', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 6, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 4, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Create a bathtub using JavaScript (preferably React). There should be a button that adds water to the tub, and a button that removes water. Bonus points if you can create this using React hooks.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Paste your GitHub repository here', 
        challengeAnswer: 'www.github.com', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional HTML experience do you have?", 
                answer: 3
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional CSS experience do you have?", 
                answer: 3
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional JavaScript experience do you have?", 
                answer: 3
            },  
            {
                question: "How many years of professional React experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence:", 
                answer: "Software nerd and foodie."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is the greatest invention?", 
                answer: "The QR code."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite novel?", 
                answer: "Breakfast of Champions"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 2, 
        userId: 7, 
        candidateName: 'Craig Rogers', 
        company: 'Forbes', 
        role: 'Copywriter ', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 8, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 2, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Write 500 words on how NFTs are disrupting the entertainment industry.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Submit a link to your Google doc here',
        challengeAnswer: 'docs.google.com/my-document', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional copywriting experience do you have?", 
                answer: 6
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional agency experience do you have?", 
                answer: 4
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence", 
                answer: "Writer, chef, and entrepreneur"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favorite movie?", 
                answer: "The Godfather"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite online publication?", 
                answer: "The Atlantic"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 2, 
        userId: 8, 
        candidateName: 'Karen Parker', 
        company: 'Forbes', 
        role: 'Copywriter ', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 6, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 2, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Write 500 words on how NFTs are disrupting the entertainment industry.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Submit a link to your Google doc here',
        challengeAnswer: 'docs.google.com/my-document', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional copywriting experience do you have?", 
                answer: 3
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional agency experience do you have?", 
                answer: 4
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence", 
                answer: "Creative writer with background in social media management."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favorite movie?", 
                answer: "Star Wars"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite online publication?", 
                answer: "The Verge"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: '', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 2, 
        userId: 9, 
        candidateName: 'Alan Russell', 
        company: 'Forbes', 
        role: 'Copywriter ', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 7, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 2, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Write 500 words on how NFTs are disrupting the entertainment industry.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Submit a link to your Google doc here',
        challengeAnswer: 'docs.google.com/my-document', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional copywriting experience do you have?", 
                answer: 5
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional agency experience do you have?", 
                answer: 5
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence", 
                answer: "Love to write and learn."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favorite movie?", 
                answer: "Pulp Fiction"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite online publication?", 
                answer: "IndieWire"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 2, 
        userId: 10, 
        candidateName: 'Karen Rodriguez', 
        company: 'Forbes', 
        role: 'Copywriter ', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 4, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 2, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Write 500 words on how NFTs are disrupting the entertainment industry.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Submit a link to your Google doc here',
        challengeAnswer: 'docs.google.com/my-document', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional copywriting experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional agency experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence", 
                answer: "Copywriter with an interest in law."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favorite movie?", 
                answer: "Forrest Gump"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite online publication?", 
                answer: "New York Times"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 2, 
        userId: 11, 
        candidateName: 'Martin Robinson', 
        company: 'Forbes', 
        role: 'Copywriter ', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 7, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 2, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Write 500 words on how NFTs are disrupting the entertainment industry.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Submit a link to your Google doc here',
        challengeAnswer: 'docs.google.com', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional copywriting experience do you have?", 
                answer: 6
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional agency experience do you have?", 
                answer: 6
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence", 
                answer: "PHD in English, professional copywriter for many years."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favorite movie?", 
                answer: "The Good, the bad, and the ugly."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite online publication?", 
                answer: "LA Times"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 2, 
        userId: 12, 
        candidateName: 'Cheryl Long', 
        company: 'Forbes', 
        role: 'Copywriter ', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 7, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 2, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Write 500 words on how NFTs are disrupting the entertainment industry.', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Submit a link to your Google doc here',
        challengeAnswer: 'docs.google.com/my-document', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional copywriting experience do you have?", 
                answer: 3
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional agency experience do you have?", 
                answer: 4
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence", 
                answer: "Copywriter with experience in the fashion industry."
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favorite movie?", 
                answer: "Mulholland Drive"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite online publication?", 
                answer: "Vogue"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 3, 
        userId: 13, 
        candidateName: 'Bill Moore', 
        company: 'Instagram', 
        role: 'UX Designer', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 6, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 5, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Create wireframes for a landing page, login page, and dashboard for a file-sharing application (i.e. dropbox).', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Submit a link to your Figma files here',
        challengeAnswer: 'www.figma.com/my-file', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional UX design experience do you have?", 
                answer: 4
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional Figma experience do you have?", 
                answer: 3
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional agency experience do you have?", 
                answer: 4
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence:", 
                answer: "Designer with a passion for clean wireframes."
            }, 
            {
                question: "Who is your favorite visual artist?", 
                answer: "Banksy"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite travel destination?", 
                answer: "Miami"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 3, 
        userId: 14, 
        candidateName: 'Janie Sullivan', 
        company: 'Instagram', 
        role: 'UX Designer', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 5, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 5, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Create wireframes for a landing page, login page, and dashboard for a file-sharing application (i.e. dropbox).', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Submit a link to your Figma files here',
        challengeAnswer: 'www.figma.com/my-file', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional UX design experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional Figma experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional agency experience do you have?", 
                answer: 3
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence:", 
                answer: "Copywriter turned UX designer"
            }, 
            {
                question: "Who is your favorite visual artist?", 
                answer: "Van Gogh"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite travel destination?", 
                answer: "Paris"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 3, 
        userId: 15, 
        candidateName: 'Andy Parker', 
        company: 'Instagram', 
        role: 'UX Designer', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 6, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 5, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Create wireframes for a landing page, login page, and dashboard for a file-sharing application (i.e. dropbox).', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Submit a link to your Figma files here',
        challengeAnswer: 'www.figma.com/my-file', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional UX design experience do you have?", 
                answer: 1
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional Figma experience do you have?", 
                answer: 1
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional agency experience do you have?", 
                answer: 3
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence:", 
                answer: "Artist who loves to design websites"
            }, 
            {
                question: "Who is your favorite visual artist?", 
                answer: "Roy Lichenstein"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite travel destination?", 
                answer: "Bahamas"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }, 
    {
        id: 3, 
        userId: 16, 
        candidateName: 'Jeannie Burton', 
        company: 'Instagram', 
        role: 'UX Designer', 
        location: 'Remote', 
        match: 7, 
        estimatedCompletionTime: 5, 
        challengeQuestion: 'Create wireframes for a landing page, login page, and dashboard for a file-sharing application (i.e. dropbox).', 
        challengeAnswerLabel: 'Submit a link to your Figma files here',
        challengeAnswer: 'www.figma.com/my-file', 
        resume: null, 
        professionalQuestions: [
            {
                question: "How many years of professional UX design experience do you have?", 
                answer: 4
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional Figma experience do you have?", 
                answer: 4
            }, 
            {
                question: "How many years of professional agency experience do you have?", 
                answer: 2
            }
        ], 
        personalityQuestions: [
            {
                question: "Describe yourself in one sentence:", 
                answer: "UX/UI designer and front end developer."
            }, 
            {
                question: "Who is your favorite visual artist?", 
                answer: "Jackson Pollack"
            }, 
            {
                question: "What is your favovorite travel destination?", 
                answer: "Hawaii"
            }, 
        ], 
        additional: 'Hire Me!', 
    }
]